

TECHNOLOGY STACK

LANGUAGES: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, SASS, SQL

LIBRARY: React, Redux, React Router FRAMEWORKS: Express, Jest, mocha

LINTERS: Stylelint, ESLint BUNDLERS: Vite, Webpack, Parcel DATABASES: PostgreSQL, MongoDB TOOLS: Git, GitHub, Docker, Lerna

ENVIRONMENTS: Node.JS, SSR

EDITORS: VS Code, WebStorm, XCode

PLATFORMS: MacOS, Linux, Windows, iOS, Android

VIDEO: After Effects, Premiere DESIGN: Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator

MANAGEMENT: JIRA, Slack, Discord, Trello, Notion

DANIL EVDOSHCHENKO

Front-end Developer

Batumi, GE E-mail: <u>ev8ko@icloud.com</u>

Telegram: ev8ko

Site: evdoshchenko.com

PROFILE

3+ years of web development experience. Expert knowledge working with HTML5, CSS3, JS and TS. Experience with React, Redux, Express. Familiar with NPM, Docker, Node.JS, SQL. Understanding of SSR and Automation testing. Using version control like Git. Experienced with the Agile/ Scrum development model. Technical and documentational skills enable the development of clarify and structable code. 12+ years of experience in computer Design. Great attention to detail and be highly organized. Effective as both an independent and team worker. Ability to handle multiple tasks under tight deadlines. Strong remote working communication skills

EDUCATION

Baltic State Technical University / <u>VOENMEH</u> - Saint Petersburg, RF 2005 - 2011 Software Engineer, MS in Information Systems and Technology

Additional / 2019 - Current

- Middle Front-End Developer, Yandex
- JavaScript+React, Petrichenko
- QA, Portnov Computer School

LANGUAGES

Russian - Fluent English - Upper Intermediate

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER / <u>Digital Agency One-Touch</u> - Moscow, RF 09.2021 - Current

- Maintaining and improving customer and partner facing web sites
- Developing new components and improve existing to provide enhanced user experience
- Ability to rapidly convert visual mockups into functional, visually elegant applications
- Producing clean, efficient, maintainable and testable code based on specification

DEVELOPER, CO-FOUNDER / <u>Applications Danilynx</u> - Batumi, GE 04.2019 - Current

- Creating, maintaining and improving customer and partner facing web applications
 • Working with business stakeholders to move new applications
- and features from concept to implementationWorking with developers and QA to build high quality, compatible and scalable solutions
- Developing UI components using modern languages and frameworks

FOUNDER / <u>Design Group GnBob</u> - Batumi, GE 10.2010 - Current

- Building and leading a team of creative professionals with backgrounds in copywriting, motion graphics, social and web design, video production
 • Leading the creative process from idea to implementation
- translating marketing objectives into clear creative stratégies
 Producing innovative solutions for branding, style guides and other deliverables for use in projects, including print, digital, social media, web

SENIOR DESIGNER / <u>Professional Football Club CSKA</u> - Moscow, RF 01.2018 - 06.2021

- Developing the graphic elements and content of communications materials
- Preparing sketches, layouts and graphic elements Establishing guidelines for illustrators or photographers Co-ordinate all aspects of production for print, audio-visual or electronic materials
- Work in a multidisciplinary environment
- Supervising other designers

HEAD OF DESIGNERS / <u>Football Club Krasnodar</u> - Krasnodar, RF 11.2015 - 01.2018

- Designing wide variety of materials for external marketing use, including brochures, guides, white papers, presentations, email campaigns, website and social media banners
- Assist internál departments with graphic design needs

WEB DEVELOPER, DESIGNER / $\underline{\text{TD ArsenalTrading}}$ - Krasnodar, RF 09.2014 - 11.2015

- Maintaining and improving company's web site
- Rebranding of company, develop logo and guidelines
 Developing storyboards for electronic productions such as multimedia, interactive and digital products and television advertising and productions

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, DESIGNER / Agency "SolomonPRO" - Perm, RF 09.2012 - 07.2014

- Creating and maintaining web sites Developing android applications
- Designing of collateral material, environmental graphics, books and magazines, corporate identity and branding, from concept to completion